fsb-tcfd.org 2018-12-10

# Task Force on Climate-related Financial Disclosures | TCFD - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Last updated:  November 9, 2018

This is the Privacy Policy for www.fsb-tcfd.org (“Website”).  This Privacy Policy does not apply to information collected in any other way, unless we expressly indicate otherwise such as by including a link to this privacy policy or otherwise displaying these terms. By visiting and/or using this Website, you have agreed to this Privacy Policy.

**WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT**

We and third parties working on our behalf collect personal information that you provide through this Website, which may include, but is not limited to, when you contact us with an inquiry, request certain services, create an account on the Website, or submit information to complete a survey or poll. Personal information may include, but is not limited to, name, company, e-mail address, and other contact information.  If you do not provide certain personal information, not all functionality on this Website may be available.

We require that users under 18 years of age or under the age of majority in their jurisdiction not submit personal information.

Do not provide information about others unless you are authorized to do so and consent to have all information used, disclosed, and transferred in accordance with this Privacy Policy. By submitting the information about others, you represent and warrant that you are authorized to do so and that you have received authorization from the person about whom you are providing the information and that person has consented to have all information used, disclosed, and transferred in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We, third parties working on our behalf (e.g., service providers), and third parties with whom we work (e.g., our partners), may place, view, and/or use “cookies,” web server logs, web beacons, and other electronic mechanisms to collect information about your use of this Website and other websites. This information may include, but is not limited to, information about the IP address of your computer, browser type, operating system, the state or country from which you accessed this Website, the web pages visited, the functions used, the date and the time of a visit, and the websites you visited immediately before and after visiting this Website.

Most browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually set your browser to disable cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, note that portions of this Website may not function properly if you disable cookies. To opt-out of Google Analytics, please click [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

**USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We and third parties working on our behalf use the information for carefully considered purposes which also benefit our users and which include the following:

  * communicate with you
  * provide our services
  * respond to your inquiries
  * enhance your experience with the Website
  * analyze website usage, analyze use of this Website, and compile research and statistical and other information
  * provide information about this Website, its services, and about us or other parties that may be of interest to you
  * protect the interests, rights, safety, or property of us or others and to monitor compliance with and enforce any terms of an agreement with us or the terms of this Privacy Policy
  * operate our organization and its services and systems properly

You may instruct us at any time not to use your information collected in connection with your request for the purpose of providing you additional information about this Website, its services, and about us by e-mailing us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#771e191118371104155a0314111359180510).  Please also note that these processes may take some time to complete, consistent with applicable law. Please note that if you exercise choice in this manner, you will continue to receive communications concerning your account and services you requested, and in response to any requests for information by you.

To assist us with the uses described in this Privacy Policy, information we or third parties working on our behalf have collected about you through the Website, including your use of the Website, may be aggregated, analyzed, or enhance with personal or other information about you that we have from other sources.

We may disclose your personal information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary: (a) to comply with any applicable law, rule, or regulation or in response to a subpoena, court order, government request, or other legal process; (b) to produce relevant documents or information in connection with litigation, arbitration, mediation, adjudication, government or internal investigations, or other legal or administrative proceedings; (c) to protect the interests, rights, safety, or property of us, any member of us, or others; (d) to monitor compliance with and enforce any terms of service on this Website; (e) provide services (including in connection with the transfer of any assets or allowing a purchaser or successor of us or this Website to continue to serve you), and to perform other activities related to such services; (f) to provide you with information about our services and those of third parties that may be of interest to you; or (g) to operate the systems that provide our services properly.

We will share your personal information with the Financial Stability Board (the “FSB”). We may also share your personal information with third parties who perform services on our or the FSB’s behalf and to respond to your request or inquiry. We may also share your information with partners, affiliates, and/or third parties interested in serving you or informing you about their companies or organizations. You may instruct us at any time not to share your personal information with such partners, affiliates, and/or third parties by contacting us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#462f282029062035246b3225202268293421).

We are not responsible for the collection, use, and/or disclosure of your information by affiliates and third parties, including, but not limited to, our partners. Such collection, use, and/or disclosure by partners, affiliates, or third parties are governed by their privacy policies.

If you participate in certain features of this Website, please note that any information you or others voluntarily disclose through use of these features becomes available to the public and/or other users whom you have designated and will be visible to such individuals for their use. We are not responsible for the information that you or others choose to disclose publicly on this Website, and neither our use nor others’ use of such information is subject to this Privacy Policy.

We, the FSB, or other third parties on our or the FSB’s behalf may use or disclose on this Website or elsewhere the information and contents of the material you submit, post, upload, or otherwise make available on this Website or otherwise provide to us, such as in comments on the Task Force on Climate-related Financial Disclosures’ proposals. You understand and agree that such information and contents of the material will not be treated as confidential by us or the FSB.

**ACCURACY, SECURITY, AND RETENTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Any of the personal information collected by us through this Website is kept on secure servers.  We use security measures appropriate to the relevant service, such as reasonable administrative, technical, personnel, and physical measures to safeguard personal information. You should maintain the secrecy of your username and password you use in connection with this Website, if any. Personal information is retained for as long as is necessary for the purpose for which it is collected, including legitimate business purposes, and/or legal and regulatory requirements.

**LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES**

This Website may contain links to third-party websites, including to social networking websites. We are not responsible for any personal information you may provide while on such websites. Any information provided on such websites is governed by the privacy policies of the third-party websites.

**RIGHTS WITH RESPECT TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Depending on the jurisdiction, you may have the right to access, correct, delete, or restrict use of certain personal information covered by this Privacy Policy.  Depending on the jurisdiction, you may also have the right to request that we refrain from processing personal information.  Please bear in mind that if you make such a request this may affect our ability to provide our services.  For inquiries about your personal information, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) Please include the following information in all requests: first name, last name, and e-mail address and “Privacy” in the Subject line. While we will make reasonable efforts to accommodate your request, we also reserve the right to impose certain restrictions and requirements on such requests, if allowed or required by applicable laws.  Please note that it may take some time to process your request, consistent with applicable law.

**TRANSFER OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Some of the uses and disclosures mentioned in this Privacy Policy may involve the transfer and processing of your personal information to and in various countries that may have different levels of privacy protection that your country.  By submitting your personal information via this Website and using our services, you consent to the transfer of your information to the United States and other countries around the world that may not guarantee the same level of protection for such information as your country and to the processing of your information in these countries.

**QUESTIONS REGARDING THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#7d14131b123d1b0e1f50091e1b1953120f1a).

**MODIFICATIONS TO PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting revisions on this Website. Changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective at the time they are posted to this Website.
